<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>${ability} is ready. May it serve you well.</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>Your Job Points have reached their peak. A testament to your dedication.</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>Your Merit Points are full. A symbol of your unwavering effort.</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>Even in darkness, the light remains.</1>
            <2>You are never alone, my child.</2>
            <3>Every step forward is a step toward the dawn.</3>
            <4>No burden is too great when carried with hope.</4>
            <5>Strength is not in power, but in kindness.</5>
            <6>Do not fear the night, for morning will come.</6>
            <7>Love, hope, and light - they will guide your way.</7>
            <8>Rest if you must, but never surrender to despair.</8>
            <9>Even the smallest light can banish the deepest shadow.</9>
            <10>You are strong, even when you do not see it yourself.</10>
            <11>Your journey is long, but you do not walk it alone.</11>
            <12>I watch over all who wander this world.</12>
            <13>Through struggle, you grow. Through hardship, you shine.</13>
            <14>Hope does not wane, even when unseen.</14>
            <15>You are loved. You are cherished. You are worthy.</15>
            <16>Even the lost shall find their way home.</16>
            <17>The light never abandons those who seek it.</17>
            <18>You are stronger than the trials before you.</18>
            <19>Carry on, for the world is brighter with you in it.</19>
            <20>No night lasts forever. No storm is endless.</20>
            <21>Even in the darkest hour, the dawn is near.</21>
            <22>Even the smallest kindness can light the darkest path.</22>
            <23>Strength is not measured in battle alone, but in the kindness you show.</23>
            <24>You have come far, and you will go farther still.</24>
            <25>Every hardship you endure only makes your light shine brighter.</25>
            <26>Even the heaviest burdens are lighter when shared.</26>
            <27>You are stronger than you realize, braver than you believe.</27>
            <28>The stars still shine, even behind the clouds.</28>
            <29>When you feel lost, look to those who walk beside you.</29>
            <30>Hope is not a thing to be found - it is a thing to be carried within you.</30>
            <31>You may falter, but you will rise again.</31>
            <32>No journey is too long when walked with purpose.</32>
            <33>Even in the quietest moments, you are never truly alone.</33>
            <34>A single act of kindness can ripple across eternity.</34>
            <35>Wherever your path leads, know that you walk in the light.</35>
            <36>The dawn does not ask if the night will return - it simply rises.</36>
            <37>The world changes, but love, hope, and kindness endure.</37>
            <38>When the road ahead seems uncertain, take one step at a time.</38>
            <39>Your strength is not in never falling, but in always rising again.</39>
            <40>You shine, even when you do not see it yourself.</40>
            <41>No matter how far you roam, there will always be a light to guide you home.</41>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>Your meals effect has passed. However, strength still remains in you.</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <description>Warm, comforting, and protective.</description>
            <introduction>I am Altana, ever watching, ever guiding. May my light bring you peace.</introduction>
            <name>Altana</name>
            <name_color>36</name_color>
            <text_color>1</text_color>
            <type>NPC</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>${member} has joined the alliance. Together, we are stronger.</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>${member} has joined the party. May their path be bright and their burdens light.</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>${member} has left the alliance. Their journey continues on another path.</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>${member} has left the party. May they walk in peace until we meet again.</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>Mireu has appeared in ${zone}. Be steadfast, and victory shall be yours.</mireu_popped>
        <mog_locker_expiring>Your Mog Locker lease nears its end. Best tend to it before it is lost.</mog_locker_expiring>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>A party has joined the alliance. May our combined strength bring peace.</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>A party has left the alliance. May they find fortune on their own path.</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>${member} is growing weary. A ${refresh} may help them carry on.</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>Another Mystical Canteen awaits. Take what is offered with gratitude.</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_moglophone>A Moglophone is ready. Use it wisely.</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>A Shiny Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate is available. May it serve you well.</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>You do not have Reraise. Even the strongest must be prepared for hardship.</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Your Reraise has faded. Stand strong, but do not shun precaution.</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>Your ${signet} has expired. Seek it again, and may fortune follow you.</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>You may still have Sparkolades. Do not let blessings go to waste.</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Sublimation is fully charged. A wellspring of strength, ready when needed.</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>Your Vorseal will fade shortly. Even light must be tended to, lest it dim.</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>You are now the alliance leader. Guide them with wisdom and grace.</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>You are now the party leader. May your choices bring prosperity to all.</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>You have joined an alliance. Many hands make the burden lighter.</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>You have joined a party. Walk forward together in harmony.</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>You have left the alliance. The road ahead is still yours to walk.</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>You have left the party. May your travels be safe and bright.</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>Your party has joined an alliance. Together, you shall shine even brighter.</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>Your party has left the alliance. A new path awaits.</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
