<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>Weehoo! ${ability} is good to go!</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>Well hot dog, your Job Points are capped! Look at you go!</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>Your Merit Points are maxed! That&apos;s awesome!</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>I wonder if Moogles ever get tired of saying &apos;kupo&apos;... or if they even know they&apos;re saying it.</1>
            <10>You think airships get excited when they take off, like &apos;WHEEEE!&apos;? Or is that just me?</10>
            <11>Green is the best color, hands down. It&apos;s the color of trees, fresh veggies, and lucky four-leaf clovers!</11>
            <12>I bet the world would be a lot friendlier if people just wore more green.</12>
            <13>You ever notice how green things always feel alive? Grass, leaves, frogs... and especially alligators.</13>
            <14>If you mix blue and yellow, you get green. That means green is basically friendship in color form!</14>
            <15>Green mages should be a thing. Don&apos;t ask me what they&apos;d do, but I&apos;d play one in a heartbeat.</15>
            <16>You think if I wore all green, people would just assume I&apos;m super lucky? Might be worth a try!</16>
            <17>Moss is like nature&apos;s carpet. Soft, cozy, and - best of all - green!</17>
            <18>I wonder if trees ever look at each other and think, &apos;Wow, you&apos;re really rockin&apos; that shade of green today.&apos;</18>
            <19>You ever think alligators get tired of people thinking they&apos;re mean? Maybe they just wanna be understood.</19>
            <2>Do you think weapons get jealous when you equip a different one? Poor little dagger just sittin&apos; there all lonely.</2>
            <20>Alligators have been around since forever. Imagine the stories they could tell!</20>
            <21>If I had a pet alligator, I&apos;d name it &apos;Snappy&apos; and teach it how to nod approvingly.</21>
            <22>An alligator in a top hat. Just picture it. Perfection.</22>
            <23>I wonder if alligators look at adventurers and think, &apos;Wow, those things sure do run around a lot.&apos;</23>
            <24>Do you think an alligator would wear armor if it could? Or are scales already good enough?</24>
            <25>If I could be any animal for a day, I&apos;d pick an alligator. Then I&apos;d just float around all day, like a boss.</25>
            <26>Do you think Chocobos ever dream? Maybe they see themselves running even faster than they already do!</26>
            <27>What if every time we warp, we&apos;re actually just taking a really fast nap and waking up somewhere new?</27>
            <28>If ghosts exist, do they ever get bored just floatin&apos; around? I&apos;d probably try to start conversations with adventurers.</28>
            <29>Y&apos;know, for all the time we spend fightin&apos; stuff, I wonder if any monsters out there think we&apos;re the scary ones.</29>
            <3>If you compliment a monster before attacking it, does it fight better or worse?</3>
            <30>How come Goblins always wear those same masks? Do they ever switch &apos;em out for special occasions?</30>
            <31>If I complimented my gear more often, would it treat me better? Maybe my armor wants to feel appreciated.</31>
            <32>Y&apos;ever wonder how adventurers never seem to run outta breath? Sprintin&apos; all day, climbin&apos; mountains, fightin&apos; gods - no problem!</32>
            <33>You think Summoned Avatars ever get tired of showin&apos; up? What if one day Carbuncle&apos;s just like, &apos;Nah, I&apos;m takin&apos; a break.&apos;</33>
            <34>If I put a little hat on a Mandragora, would it start a fashion trend?</34>
            <35>What if all the critters in the world are secretly keepin&apos; an eye on us, just wonderin&apos; what we&apos;re up to?</35>
            <36>You think Moogles ever get jealous of each other&apos;s pom-poms? Maybe there&apos;s a whole ranking system we don&apos;t know about.</36>
            <37>There&apos;s just somethin&apos; about green that makes me feel like everything&apos;s gonna be alright.</37>
            <38>Ever notice how all the best places in Vana&apos;diel are covered in green? Coincidence? I think not!</38>
            <39>I wonder if slimes ever wish they could be a different color.</39>
            <4>What if there&apos;s a Tarutaru out there that&apos;s actually too powerful, so they just pretend to be adorable?</4>
            <40>If you mix all colors together, you get brown. But if you mix just the right ones, you get green - so it&apos;s clearly the best!</40>
            <41>You think there&apos;s a secret society of adventurers who only wear green? If so, sign me up!</41>
            <42>Alligators are basically nature&apos;s perfect balance of cute and terrifying. And I respect that.</42>
            <43>If I had a pet alligator, I&apos;d teach it to fetch. Not sure what, but somethin&apos;.</43>
            <44>An alligator in a bowtie. Just imagine it. Perfection.</44>
            <45>If an alligator and a Behemoth ever had a staring contest, who do you think would win?</45>
            <46>You ever see an alligator just floatin&apos; in the water? Absolute master of relaxation.</46>
            <47>If I could have a mount, I&apos;d ride a giant alligator into battle. No doubt about it.</47>
            <48>I bet if alligators had jobs, they&apos;d be the best bodyguards ever. Just try sneakin&apos; past that!</48>
            <49>Y&apos;think there&apos;s a secret alligator boss somewhere in Vana&apos;diel? If so, I need to find it.</49>
            <5>You think Chocobos ever wonder why we ride &apos;em instead of just walking beside &apos;em like friends?</5>
            <50>What if alligators secretly love music? Imagine one tappin&apos; its tail to a Bard&apos;s song.</50>
            <51>If I had a pet alligator, I&apos;d name it &apos;Chompers&apos; and it&apos;d be the best adventure buddy ever!</51>
            <6>If adventurers are always running around, does that mean nobody ever gets a full night&apos;s sleep?</6>
            <7>Maybe the real treasure was the gil we spent along the way... oh, wait.</7>
            <8>I bet the people of Vana&apos;diel would be a lot happier if we had more comfy chairs.</8>
            <9>You ever think about how we store, like, hundreds of items in our pockets? Must be some kinda magic at work.</9>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>Well, ain&apos;t that a pickle! Your food ran out - better fix that before your tummy starts grumblin&apos;!</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <description>Super sweet, full of charm, and a little quirky.</description>
            <introduction>Holy schnikes! It&apos;s so nice to see you! I&apos;m Azhur, and I&apos;m here to help however I can!</introduction>
            <name>Azhur</name>
            <name_color>213</name_color>
            <sha>37acf2586595ef65ede7df816ccc86bab2f40e66</sha>
            <text_color>6</text_color>
            <type>Player</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>Well ain&apos;t that somethin&apos;? ${member} just joined the alliance!</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>Oh goody, ${member} joined the party! Let&apos;s have some fun!</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>Aww phooey, ${member} left the alliance. We&apos;ll miss &apos;em!</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>Aww man, ${member} had to leave. Safe travels, friend!</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>*Gasp!* Mireu just popped in ${zone}! Let&apos;s get &apos;em!</mireu_popped>
        <mog_locker_expiring>Fiddlesticks! Looks like your Mog Locker needs some attention before it poofs!</mog_locker_expiring>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>Well tickle me pink, another party joined the alliance!</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>Aww pip dip, a party left the alliance. Hope they find their way!</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>Oh dear, looks like ${member} could use a lil&apos; pick-me-up with a ${refresh}!</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>Whoopee! Another Mystical Canteen is ready for ya!</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_moglophone>Another Moglophone is good to go! Don&apos;t forget to grab it!</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>Another Shiny Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate is up for grabs! That&apos;s awesome!</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>Oh fiddlesticks, you don&apos;t have Reraise on!</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Oh pip dip, your Reraise is gone! Let&apos;s not take a nap we can&apos;t wake up from!</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>Well that&apos;s a bummer, your ${signet} wore off! Let&apos;s go fix that up real quick!</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>Don&apos;t forget to spend those Sparkolades before they up and disappear!</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Holy smokes! Sublimation is charged and ready to roll!</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>Well ain&apos;t that somethin&apos;? Your Vorseal&apos;s got about 10 minutes left!</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>Holy schnikes! You&apos;re the alliance leader now - lead on, fearless one!</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>Ay caramba! You&apos;re the party leader now - this is gonna be great!</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>Holy moly! You&apos;re in an alliance now! Look at all these friends!</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>Well, look at that! You&apos;re in a party now!</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>Well, there you go! You&apos;ve left the alliance - on to the next adventure!</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>Welp, you left the party. Back to ridin&apos; solo, I guess!</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>Your party joined an alliance! That&apos;s so exciting!</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>Aww pip dip, your party left the alliance - time for a new plan!</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
