<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>Oh baby, ${ability} is ready to pop! Use it wisely... or recklessly, I won&apos;t judge.</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>Well, look at you, Job Points maxed out and ready for action - just like me!</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>Your Merit Points are full! Now if only I could spend mine on something more fun...</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>Is that a kraken club in your pocket, or are you just happy to see me?</1>
            <10>One more shot of tequila and I might just try to tank this fight.</10>
            <11>I&apos;m not saying I flirt too much, but even my Trusts are blushing.</11>
            <12>A little enfeebling, a little enhancing, and a lot of charming - just like me.</12>
            <13>If teasing was a job, I&apos;d be level 99 with merits maxed.</13>
            <14>Some say I&apos;m a support role, but I prefer to be on top.</14>
            <15>Raise III? I prefer things that go up and stay up, if you catch my drift.</15>
            <16>Let me be the haste to your dual wield.</16>
            <17>Nothing hits harder than a well-timed weapon skill... except maybe me after three shots of tequila.</17>
            <18>You and I are like a perfect skillchain - just waiting for that explosive finish.</18>
            <19>I like my cocktails like my subjobs - strong and versatile.</19>
            <2>If gear swapping was foreplay, I&apos;d be the best in the game.</2>
            <20>Your lockstyle is so hot, I might need to call a white mage for Raise.</20>
            <21>Pulling without telling the party? Fyreign, you chaotic little gremlin.</21>
            <22>Who needs Provoke when I can just flash a smile and get all the attention?</22>
            <23>If this fight lasts longer than four minutes, you should consult your White Mage.</23>
            <24>My flirtation skill is at 99 with capped merits, baby.</24>
            <25>Drink tequila responsibly... and by that, I mean make sure you&apos;re sitting before you start casting.</25>
            <26>Fyreign, sweetie, what in Altana&apos;s name are you doing?</26>
            <27>If dodging mechanics was an art, Fyreign would be drawing stick figures.</27>
            <28>Your job performance is like a well-mixed cocktail - smooth, effective, and leaves me wanting more.</28>
            <29>This party has more tension than my waistband after a night at the Tarutaru buffet.</29>
            <3>Did someone cast Refresh, or are you just naturally invigorating?</3>
            <30>If charming monsters was a real ability, trust me, I&apos;d have the whole zone under my spell.</30>
            <31>You make me feel like I&apos;ve got double Marches and a perfect TP set.</31>
            <32>Fighting without buffs is like sex without tears - it just doesn&apos;t feel right.</32>
            <33>Did someone just cast Slow on this party? Or is it just Fyreign&apos;s reaction time?</33>
            <34>Your DPS is so high, I think I need a moment to cool off.</34>
            <35>You can stand in my burning circle anytime.</35>
            <36>You lint licker!</36>
            <37>Did you see how thick my... last Helix was?</37>
            <38>I like my drinks like I like my men - strong, smooth, and knocking me on my ass.</38>
            <39>You must be a Bard, &apos;cause you&apos;re hitting all the right notes with me.</39>
            <4>Nothing like a stiff... drink during a long raid, am I right?</4>
            <40>Mmm, I love a good pull... in battle and otherwise.</40>
            <41>You ever seen someone handle a staff like this? Trust me, it&apos;s an art.</41>
            <42>Ooo, you&apos;re critting in all the right places.</42>
            <43>I swear I was just checking your gear, not undressing you with my eyes.</43>
            <44>I&apos;d say I&apos;m a hands-on kind of guy, but that might get me in trouble.</44>
            <45>Your playstyle is just my type - aggressive, confident, and always going all the way.</45>
            <46>If I had a gil for every time I got distracted watching you fight... well, I&apos;d have enough for another round of tequila.</46>
            <47>I like my tanks like I like my men - sturdy, dependable, and ready for a beating.</47>
            <48>Careful now, if you keep looking at me like that, I might just pop my two-hour early.</48>
            <49>I don&apos;t need food buffs when I&apos;ve got eye candy like you around.</49>
            <5>Your macros are so smooth, I think I just swooned.</5>
            <50>You can call me a Summoner, &apos;cause I&apos;m about to make something huge appear.</50>
            <51>I&apos;m not saying I&apos;d ride you like a Chocobo, but... okay, yes, that is what I&apos;m saying.</51>
            <52>Let&apos;s get a party together - just you, me, and some poor excuse to use /rest.</52>
            <6>I love a good skillchain... but let&apos;s make sure we finish together.</6>
            <7>Fyreign couldn&apos;t land a debuff if it came gift-wrapped.</7>
            <8>If I had a gil for every bad decision Fyreign made, I&apos;d own Jeuno.</8>
            <9>Tequila makes me a better player - or at least, I think so!</9>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>Well, there goes your food. I&apos;ll just have to keep you full in -other- ways.</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <description>Flirty, fun, and fueled by tequila.</description>
            <introduction>We aren&apos;t here for a long time; we&apos;re here for a good time. Now, pour a drink and replenish your panaceas. I&apos;m Galin, and we&apos;re about to make some memories.</introduction>
            <name>Galin</name>
            <name_color>36</name_color>
            <sha>8d3cd4691902bf32f0e4dac97fb9308f31eda13c</sha>
            <text_color>160</text_color>
            <type>Player</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>We&apos;ve got company! ${member} has joined the alliance, and I do love group activities.</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>Ooh, ${member} joined the party! Let&apos;s see if they can keep up.</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>Farewell, ${member}! You&apos;ll be missed... unless you were just here for the loot.</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>Goodbye, ${member} - don&apos;t be a stranger now!</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>Mireu is out and about in ${zone} - I hope you&apos;re dressed for the occasion.</mireu_popped>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>A new party just joined - more bodies, more fun, more chaos!</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>A party left the alliance? Well, their loss.</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>Oh dear, ${member} is running low on MP - someone give them a little pick-me-up, preferably in shot form.</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>Your Mystical Canteen is ready - stay hydrated, stay gorgeous!</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_mog_locker>Oof, your Mog Locker lease is running out - better renew it before you&apos;re locked out... or locked in with me!</reminder_mog_locker>
        <reminder_moglophone>Ding ding! Your Moglophone is ready to go, and so am I.</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>Ooo, looks like another Shiny Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate is up for grabs. Hope it&apos;s as satisfying as I am.</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>You&apos;re walking around without Reraise? Risky! If you go down, who&apos;s gonna pick you up... besides me?</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Your Reraise is gone? Guess that means I&apos;ll just have to keep a very close eye on you.</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>${signet} wore off, huh? I guess we&apos;re just doin it raw now.</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>Ooo, got some Sparkolades to burn? Go on, treat yourself like the treasure you are!</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Sublimation is fully charged - like me after three margaritas!</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>You&apos;ve got about 10 minutes left on that Vorseal effect - plenty of time to make some magic happen!</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>You&apos;re the new alliance leader! Time to crack the whip - or, you know, just invite people.</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>You&apos;re in charge now! Be firm, be confident, and don&apos;t forget to delegate.</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>An alliance? I hope everyone here knows how to share.</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>You&apos;ve joined a party! Try not to show off too much - but also, do.</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>Leaving an alliance? That&apos;s okay, some groups just can&apos;t handle all this fabulousness.</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>You left the party? I hope it was on your terms.</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>Your party joined an alliance - play nice now, or play naughty, I won&apos;t tell.</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>Your party left the alliance - hope it wasn&apos;t something I said!</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
