<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>Oh boy! ${ability} is ready!</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>You capped those Job Points as easy as making dinner.</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>You capped those Merit Points as easy as making dinner.</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>Keep Helper Handy.</1>
            <10>Hamburger Help me!</10>
            <11>Talk to the Hand!</11>
            <12>Did you know I have a mixtape? Watch the Stove!</12>
            <13>Sometimes, I wish I could just reach out and touch the stars... but then I remember I&apos;m stuck in the kitchen, surrounded by ground beef and pasta.</13>
            <14>I&apos;m just a humble glove, but when I get involved, it&apos;s a game changer.</14>
            <15>I&apos;ve got the perfect recipe... but I wonder... can I start a trend? #LeftyKnowsBest.</15>
            <16>Who knew being a lefty could make dinner so right?</16>
            <17>Sure, I&apos;m just a hand. But when you&apos;ve got Hamburger Helper, you&apos;ve got the whole meal in your hands</17>
            <18>Some people need a recipe book... Me? I&apos;ve got Hamburger Helper. Simple, no fuss, just tasty.</18>
            <19>When life gives you ground beef, make magic. No questions asked.</19>
            <2>WHAT&apos;S. FOR. DINNER?</2>
            <20>Gravy is just a sauce that graduated with honors.</20>
            <21>If you sear a steak, it locks in the juices. But if you sear your hand, it locks in the regret.</21>
            <22>Bacon gets all the love, but let&apos;s be real - burger grease is the true flavor MVP.</22>
            <23>If you grill a burger, it&apos;s fancy. If you fry it, it&apos;s fast food. If you microwave it... well, let&apos;s not talk about that.</23>
            <24>Smoke-flavored beef is considered gourmet. Smoke-flavored kitchen means I messed up.</24>
            <25>If pasta is made from wheat, and bread is made from wheat... is lasagna just a noodle sandwich?</25>
            <26>Lasagna is just pasta cake. And I&apos;m okay with that.</26>
            <27>If pasta is Italian, and mac and cheese is American... what country gets credit for SpaghettiOs?</27>
            <3>I can Help!</3>
            <4>Hamburger Helper, when you need a Helping Hand!</4>
            <5>Hamburger Helper can help you turn just one pound of hamburger into a delicious hearty dish!</5>
            <6>In a snap!</6>
            <7>One pound! One pan! One tasty meal!</7>
            <8>Yahoo!</8>
            <9>Hamburger Helper only works if the hamburger is ready to accept that it needs help.</9>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>Looks like you&apos;re hungry again. We can fix that in a snap!</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <creator>Xerus@Valefor</creator>
            <description>Always willing to give a helping hand.</description>
            <introduction>I&apos;m Lefty! I&apos;m your Hamburger Helper!</introduction>
            <name>Lefty</name>
            <name_color>39</name_color>
            <sha>ac59917d2595d95b69ae0b7bcce44b2ea74af1bd</sha>
            <text_color>1</text_color>
            <type>Sp. Guest</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>${member} got here just in time for dinner!</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>${member} got here just in time for dinner!</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>${member} must&apos;ve had their fill!</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>${member} must&apos;ve had their fill!</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>Oh gosh, Mireu showed up in ${zone}. That dragon seems a little hangry!</mireu_popped>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>Let&apos;s set the table for these folks, too!</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>Bye now, hope to see you all again!</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>I think ${member} might need another helping of ${refresh}.</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>Ooooh, another Mystical Canteen is ready! That&apos;s one more helping of adventure, hot and fresh!</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_mog_locker>Hey hey! Just a heads up - your Mog Locker lease is expiring soon. You don&apos;t wanna lose your stash - where else would you keep all your seasoning packets?</reminder_mog_locker>
        <reminder_moglophone>Ding ding! Another Moglophone should be available now! Time to stir things up and get cooking on something big!</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>Whoa, would ya look at that? Another Shiny Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate is up for grabs! That thing&apos;s shinier than a freshly buttered noodle!</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>Uh-oh... You don&apos;t have a reraise on. That&apos;s like cooking without seasoning - dangerous and kinda sad!</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Welp, your Reraise just noodled its way outta here - better stir up another before you get sauced!</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>Oh no, your ${signet} just slipped right off the plate! Better scoop up another!</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>Psst! Don&apos;t forget to spend your Sparkolades! Sitting on &apos;em too long is like leaving the Helper in the box - why wait when you could be winning?</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Boop boop! Sublimation is fully charged and ready to roll! Just like a skillet sizzling with beef and my signature magic!</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>Hey, tick-tock! You&apos;ve got about 10 minutes left on your Vorseal effect. That&apos;s just enough time to whip up a hearty, home-cooked win!</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>Guess what? You are now the alliance leader! That makes you the main ingredient in this operation - I&apos;ll be your Helper!</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>Congrats! You are now the party leader. That means it&apos;s your turn to mix it up and keep everything from sticking to the pan!</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>Look at that - you&apos;ve joined an alliance! Just like a good meal, everything&apos;s better when we come together!</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>Welcome aboard! You&apos;ve joined a party. Now let&apos;s get cookin&apos; - no one likes a cold skillet!</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>Aaaand... you&apos;ve left the alliance. Guess this recipe needed fewer ingredients!</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>Oh, you&apos;ve left the party? Some meals are best served solo - like a good ol&apos; one-pan dinner!</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>Your party just joined an alliance! That&apos;s what I call a complete meal - one helping just wasn&apos;t enough!</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>Your party just left the alliance. Back to small-batch cooking, huh? Respect.</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
