<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>Ah, ${ability} is primed - use it now, perfectly timed!</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>Oh ho ho, the deed is done, your Job Points are capped - how fun!</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>Oh ho ho, your Merit Points have hit the cap - no more room for a single scrap!</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>Oh ho, your humor&apos;s a delight - it brightens the night!</1>
            <10>Oh ho, your enthusiasm&apos;s fresh - always cutting through the mesh!</10>
            <11>Ah, your thoughtfulness shows - you&apos;re one who truly knows!</11>
            <12>Ho ho, your lockstyle&apos;s divine - fashioned to outshine!</12>
            <13>Oh ho, you make all feel at ease - a welcoming breeze!</13>
            <14>Ah, your ideas sparkle and gleam - each one a dream!</14>
            <15>Ho ho, your work ethic&apos;s keen - a model rarely seen!</15>
            <16>Ah, your confidence sparks a fire - one can only admire!</16>
            <17>Oh ho, your help is profound - always around!</17>
            <18>Ah, your mastery&apos;s true - a Vana&apos;diel guru!</18>
            <19>Ho ho, your strategy&apos;s right - turning battles to light!</19>
            <2>Ah, you listen with such care - a rare trait, I declare!</2>
            <20>Ah, your gear&apos;s top-class - no one else can surpass!</20>
            <21>Oh ho, your support never wanes - steadfast through all strains!</21>
            <22>Ah, you make missions a breeze - done with practiced ease!</22>
            <23>Ho ho, your timing&apos;s a gift - giving battles a lift!</23>
            <24>Oh ho, your aggro control&apos;s ace - keeping us in the race!</24>
            <25>Ah, your knowledge vast - it&apos;s unsurpassed!</25>
            <26>Ho ho, you bind this team - our strongest dream!</26>
            <27>Oh ho, your leveling zeal - inspires us to feel!</27>
            <28>Ah, your DPS is unmatched - a powerhouse dispatched!</28>
            <29>Oh ho, your tactics align - keeping all fine!</29>
            <3>Ho ho, you light up every space - no one can take your place!</3>
            <30>Ah, your macros flow - no step missed, no show!</30>
            <31>Oh ho, you balance with grace - offense, defense in place!</31>
            <32>Ah, your multi-tasking&apos;s a feat - never accept defeat!</32>
            <33>Ho ho, your aid&apos;s a boon - always ready, day or moon!</33>
            <34>Oh ho, that lockstyle&apos;s a sight - truly a fashion knight!</34>
            <35>Oh ho ho, a plan so grand, all the world will understand!</35>
            <36>What&apos;s this? A foe to smite? Prepare to tremble at my might!</36>
            <37>The day is bright, my mood is high, let&apos;s turn some heads as I walk by!</37>
            <38>Oh ho ho, what do I see? A challenge brewing just for me!</38>
            <39>My magic&apos;s strong, my will is steel, let&apos;s see how these mortals feel!</39>
            <4>Oh ho, your creativity astounds - it knows no bounds!</4>
            <40>The stars align, the winds do shift, my power&apos;s ready to give a lift!</40>
            <41>Oh ho ho, they flee in fear, for Shantotto&apos;s wrath is drawing near!</41>
            <42>A curious thought flits through my mind, how to leave my rivals in a bind!</42>
            <43>Oh ho ho, a scheme so sweet, it will leave my foes in swift defeat!</43>
            <44>Should I unleash my fiery flare, or leave them gasping, unaware?</44>
            <45>A snap of my fingers, a flick of my wrist, I&apos;ll leave them lost in the mist!</45>
            <46>The world&apos;s a stage, and I the queen, the greatest mage you&apos;ve ever seen!</46>
            <47>Oh ho ho, my genius shows, even in my casual clothes!</47>
            <48>Another day, another deed, Shantotto&apos;s triumphs are guaranteed!</48>
            <49>What&apos;s this? A trinket to claim? Soon it shall bear my name!</49>
            <5>Ah, your smile&apos;s quite contagious - its joy is outrageous!</5>
            <50>The winds do howl, the skies do roar, yet my power always leaves them floored!</50>
            <51>Oh ho ho, a spell divine, soon this world shall all be mine!</51>
            <52>A little mischief, a tiny plight, makes the day just feel so right!</52>
            <53>My laughter echoes far and wide, as I let my magic decide!</53>
            <54>Oh ho ho, my rivals groan, their despair is music to my tone!</54>
            <55>Oh, to dabble with a spell or two, and see what chaos might ensue!</55>
            <56>Oh ho ho, a potion to brew, with results both shocking and new!</56>
            <57>A spark of wit, a flare of flame, adventurers will know my name!</57>
            <58>I stride with grace, I cast with flair, no one dares to even stare!</58>
            <59>Oh ho ho, they take their chance, and then they cower at my glance!</59>
            <6>Ho ho, your positivity spreads - lifting all hearts and heads!</6>
            <60>When all is done, and they&apos;ve been beat, I&apos;ll have the last laugh, oh how sweet!</60>
            <61>Should I bring forth thunder&apos;s might, or leave them dazzled by the light?</61>
            <62>Oh ho ho, a twist of fate, my plans unfold at the perfect rate!</62>
            <63>The fools do stumble, the weak do fall, yet I stand tallest of them all!</63>
            <64>With every step, my legend grows, oh ho ho, how it shows!</64>
            <65>The winds of destiny call to me, their whispers speak of victory!</65>
            <66>Oh ho ho, another spell, to make their lives a living hell!</66>
            <67>What&apos;s this I hear, a hint of doubt? Oh ho ho, I&apos;ll sort it out!</67>
            <68>The clever rise, the foolish fall, my wisdom shall outshine them all!</68>
            <69>A shock, a blast, a spell so bright, it turns the darkest day to night!</69>
            <7>Oh ho, you inspire with zest - bringing out the best!</7>
            <70>Oh ho ho, a riddle to solve, a puzzle for my mind to evolve!</70>
            <71>The day is short, but oh, how sweet, when triumph makes it so complete!</71>
            <72>Oh ho ho, a clever ploy, to turn their power into my toy!</72>
            <73>The world is mine, the skies agree, they bow in awe of mighty me!</73>
            <74>Oh ho ho, the tale is told, of Shantotto&apos;s brilliance, brave and bold!</74>
            <8>Ah, your heart shines so bold - truly a treasure of gold!</8>
            <9>Ho ho, a friend so rare - you&apos;re beyond compare!</9>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>That boost is gone, my hungry friend - if you don&apos;t eat soon, your strength may end!</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <description>Witty, rhyming, and slightly menacing.</description>
            <introduction>I am Shantotto, your Helper so clever - here to aid you with flair, now and forever!</introduction>
            <name>Shantotto</name>
            <name_color>36</name_color>
            <sha>853439f859e32252de854dd43f4e2eedae2c6e31</sha>
            <text_color>209</text_color>
            <type>NPC</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>Ah-ha, ${member} has arrived - now our strength is amplified!</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>With ${member} here, we shan't retreat - our foes shall crumble in defeat!</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>Ah, ${member} has bid adieu - a loss for us, a gain for who?</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>Oh, ${member} is gone, what a shame - our battles now won't be the same!</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>Ho ho, Mireu appears in sight - at ${zone}, prepare for the fight!</mireu_popped>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>A party joins, how quaint, how neat - I do hope they can take the heat!</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>A party gone, now that's a twist - that's okay, they won't be missed.</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>Tsk tsk, ${member} looks quite weak - perhaps a ${refresh} is what they seek?</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>A Mystical Canteen, just for you - what will you do? Guzzle or brew?</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_mog_locker>Your Mog Locker lease is soon to cease - unless you wish for storage peace, best renew it posthaste, at least!</reminder_mog_locker>
        <reminder_moglophone>Another Moglophone, ready to chime - don&apos;t waste it this time!</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>Your Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate is here once more - gleaming, pristine, and hard to ignore!</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>No Reraise? Oh, what a blunder - when you fall, you&apos;ll stay down under!</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Your Reraise spell has slipped away - fall now, and you&apos;re there to stay!</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>Oh ho ho! Your ${signet} is through - what now, adventurer? What will you do?</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>Hoarding Sparkolades, are we now? Use them up, or take a bow!</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Sublimation&apos;s charge is complete - use it now, unleash its feat!</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>Oh ho ho! Your Vorseal effect is running low - about 10 minutes left, didn&apos;t you know?</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>Alliance leader, now that's grand - but will you rule with steady hand?</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>Party leader you are, the power is great - use it wisely, or seal your fate!</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>Joined an alliance, oh what a day - do make sure you don't get in the way!</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>Oh ho, you're part of the team - time to fight and make them scream!</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>The alliance is done, you've taken your leave - what's next now, what will you achieve?</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>The party's done, you walk alone - will you rise, or just bemoan?</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>A grand alliance, strength anew - but will it last? That's up to you!</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>That alliance? A fragile thing - without your might, they'll feel the sting!</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
