<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<settings>
    <global>
        <ability_ready>Aw man, ${ability} is back on deck - time to show &apos;em what you got!</ability_ready>
        <capped_job_points>Aw man, you maxed out your Job Points? Now that&apos;s perty impressive!</capped_job_points>
        <capped_merit_points>Well look at you, sittin&apos; on a pile of Merit Points! That&apos;s some real noble effort right there!</capped_merit_points>
        <flavor_text>
            <1>Aw man, you&apos;re lookin&apos; perty sharp today!</1>
            <10>You&apos;re tougher than an Orc in Davoi and twice as smart!</10>
            <11>Aw man, this is perty exciting - I can feel the energy in the air!</11>
            <12>Some folks say &apos;luck&apos; - I say &apos;San d&apos;Orian determination&apos;!</12>
            <13>If I had a gil for every time Bastok lost a conquest tally, I&apos;d own my own chateau by now!</13>
            <14>Ya keep fightin&apos; like that, and you&apos;ll be the pride of San d&apos;Oria in no time!</14>
            <15>Have I mentioned that San d&apos;Oria&apos;s got the best smiths? Not like those rusty ol&apos; Bastokan scraps.</15>
            <16>Aw man, your gear is lookin&apos; perty slick - fit for royalty!</16>
            <17>You ever just stop and admire the craftsmanship of San d&apos;Orian armor?</17>
            <18>Aw man, you see that move? That was downright noble!</18>
            <19>Ain&apos;t nothin&apos; like a good day in San d&apos;Oria - blue skies, noble folk, and a perty castle!</19>
            <2>You got that San d&apos;Orian spirit - classy and strong!</2>
            <20>You ever just stop and listen to the San d&apos;Orian anthem? Gives me chills every time!</20>
            <21>San d&apos;Oria&apos;s got the best views, the best food, and the best people!</21>
            <22>Aw man, the scent of fresh-baked San d&apos;Orian bread in the morning? Nothin&apos; beats it!</22>
            <23>Some people use maps, but a real San d&apos;Orian just follows their instincts!</23>
            <24>Ya ever notice how everything in Bastok is just... brown? Even their spirits seem a little dusty!</24>
            <25>I hear in Bastok, they call rust &apos;industrial seasoning&apos;</25>
            <26>The way you play, it&apos;s like you got a San d&apos;Orian Prince&apos;s confidence!</26>
            <27>You ever see a Bastokan knight? Yeah, me neither!</27>
            <28>Y&apos;know, I swear these dice are rigged. Probably made in Bastok...</28>
            <29>I think I&apos;m goin skiing this weekend!</29>
            <3>Y&apos;know, if you ever get tired of all that soot in Bastok, San d&apos;Oria&apos;s got open fields and fresh air.</3>
            <30>I knew it!</30>
            <31>Hmmm... which Rostam should I use today?</31>
            <32>Even a bad roll looks good with the right lockstytle.</32>
            <33>High-fives and butt slaps all around!</33>
            <34>My next Wild Card is gonna be a 6, I guarantee it!</34>
            <4>Ain&apos;t nothin&apos; better than a crisp morning in Ronfaure!</4>
            <5>Aw man, you&apos;re fightin&apos; like a true knight of San d&apos;Oria!</5>
            <6>You ever just sit back and admire the flags in San d&apos;Oria? Real noble-lookin&apos;, ain&apos;t they?</6>
            <7>Bastok&apos;s got machines, sure, but San d&apos;Oria&apos;s got history, honor, and bagpipes!</7>
            <8>You ever try a fresh Elshimo coconut? Not as good as San d&apos;Orian wine, but still perty tasty!</8>
            <9>Y&apos;know, people in San d&apos;Oria walk with purpose! Unlike Bastok where they just shuffle in the dust.</9>
        </flavor_text>
        <food_wears_off>Your food ran out quicker than a Bastokan when the check is due!</food_wears_off>
        <info>
            <description>Super nice guy, loves San d&apos;Oria maybe a little too much.</description>
            <introduction>Hello, hello! The name&apos;s Sigue, and I&apos;m here to help ya!</introduction>
            <name>Sigue</name>
            <name_color>36</name_color>
            <sha>36c90f2ffaa0385ca6d998c44f2154dcab9c9abb</sha>
            <text_color>39</text_color>
            <type>Player</type>
        </info>
        <member_joined_alliance>Aw man, ${member} just hopped into the alliance - things are gettin&apos; exciting now!</member_joined_alliance>
        <member_joined_party>Hey now, ${member} just joined up! This party&apos;s lookin&apos; perty solid!</member_joined_party>
        <member_left_alliance>Well shoot, ${member} stepped out. Hope they ain&apos;t headin&apos; to Bastok...</member_left_alliance>
        <member_left_party>Well shoot, ${member} just left.</member_left_party>
        <mireu_popped>Aw man, Mireu just got spotted in ${zone}! Let&apos;s get in there!</mireu_popped>
        <other_party_joined_alliance>Aw man, we got another group in here - things are about to get fun!</other_party_joined_alliance>
        <other_party_left_alliance>Welp, that other party packed up and left. Hope they&apos;re headin&apos; to San d&apos;Oria and not, y&apos;know, Bastok.</other_party_left_alliance>
        <party_low_mp>Looks like ${member} could use a lil&apos; pick-me-up. Somebody got a ${refresh} handy?</party_low_mp>
        <reminder_canteen>Another Mystical Canteen is ready - now go quench that thirst!</reminder_canteen>
        <reminder_mog_locker>Ah, dang it, your Mog Locker lease is almost up! If this were San d&apos;Oria, you&apos;d get a proper vault.</reminder_mog_locker>
        <reminder_moglophone>Well hey now, another Moglophone! Just don&apos;t let Bastok hear about it!</reminder_moglophone>
        <reminder_plate>Ooooh, that&apos;s a good-lookin&apos; Ra&apos;Kaznarian Plate! Go on and grab it!</reminder_plate>
        <reraise_check>Oh lordy, you&apos;re running around without Reraise? That&apos;s a Bastokan move if I ever saw one!</reraise_check>
        <reraise_wears_off>Oh no, your Reraise wore off! Better get that back on before you end up in Bastok!</reraise_wears_off>
        <signet_wears_off>Well now, that ain&apos;t great - you lost ${signet}! Hope you got a friendly guard nearby!</signet_wears_off>
        <sparkolade_reminder>Sittin&apos; on all them Sparkolades? Better spend &apos;em before some Bastoker tries to steal &apos;em!</sparkolade_reminder>
        <sublimation_charged>Hey now, Sublimation&apos;s topped off and ready to roll!</sublimation_charged>
        <vorseal_wearing>Your Vorseal&apos;s got about 10 minutes left - make &apos;em count!</vorseal_wearing>
        <you_are_now_alliance_leader>Aw man, you&apos;re the alliance leader now! You&apos;re like San d&apos;Orian royalty!</you_are_now_alliance_leader>
        <you_are_now_party_leader>Well look at that, you&apos;re in charge now! A true leader, San d&apos;Orian style!</you_are_now_party_leader>
        <you_joined_alliance>Aw man, you&apos;re in an alliance now! This is gonna be perty epic!</you_joined_alliance>
        <you_joined_party>Aw man, you&apos;re in a party now! Time to have some fun!</you_joined_party>
        <you_left_alliance>Well dang, alliance fun&apos;s over for now. Back to solo life!</you_left_alliance>
        <you_left_party>Well, there ya go - off on your own again.</you_left_party>
        <your_party_joined_alliance>Aw man, our parties just linked up - this is gonna be perty good!</your_party_joined_alliance>
        <your_party_left_alliance>Welp, back to just the party. Ain&apos;t nothin&apos; wrong with that!</your_party_left_alliance>
    </global>
</settings>
